Call an ambulance.
Now you see why I
didn't call an ambulance.
How badly does the Director
want this war funded?
There are literally
thousands of soldiers
in the jungle waiting for me
to deliver supplies and weapons.
You really think you're
the guy to step into this?
I want back in the game.
I ain't never scored blow before.
- I know a guy.
- He's kind of crazy.
Okay. front me a key.
You got one day to bring me $12.000.
- What is that?
- Nothing.
- Go home. Mel.
- Come on. Franklin.
Go home.
I just wanna offer you
the product I'm selling.
I'm not here to start any trouble...
Bullshit!
_
Franklin Saint.
You ever need anything.
you come find me.
Okay. Franklin Saint.
Get the fuck out of here.
Most of that goes towards
the next shipment. okay.
So don't get too attached.
You have the balls to come in
here after running to daddy?
There's got to be a way I can do this
without ending up dead or in jail.
In your own hood. they
can't afford no blow.
See that? See those rocks?
We gonna make bank.
It's gonna be 13 a key.
You have somebody stake
out his little crib.
Get right to the source.
There's bills and the mortgage.
You ain't gotta worry about
any of that anymore. Mom.
I don't want your reefer money.
Aw. shit.
Leon!
It ain't about payback. all right?
Why don't you think about
taking care of your people?
Your folk.
Come on. Ray Ray.
- Ray Ray. man. come on!
- Do it. motherfucker!
- All right. all right!
- Ray Ray! Ray Ray!
- Do it!
- Ray Ray! Ray...
Just wanted to say I'm sorry.
About everything.
Make sure he gets home safe.
This is war. Teddy.
You need to learn to let things go.
The Director's very proud of you.
So is the president.
_
My fellow Americans.
I must speak to you tonight
about a mounting danger
in Central America that threatens
the security of the United States.
The plan to aid rebels fighting
the Nicaraguan government
is in trouble in the House.
The administration has given the Contras
at least $100 million
in the last five years.
And they can't even tell us
how that money was spent.
If we cut off the freedom fighters
we will be giving the Soviets
one of their greatest
foreign policy victories
since World War II.
What the administration is asking for
on behalf of freedom
in Central America...
Is so small. so minimal.
considering what is at stake.
The total amount requested for aid
to all of Central America...
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
♪ All the leaves are brown ♪
♪ And the sky is gray ♪
♪ I've been for a walk ♪
♪ On a winter's day ♪
♪ I'd be safe and warm ♪
♪ If I was in LA ♪
Money.
Yuda. get the kid his bricks.
♪ Ooh. California dreamin' ♪
♪ On such a winter's day ♪
Who wants free ice cream?
♪ I'd still be a
California dreamer ♪
♪ I'm searching for my mind ♪
♪ Searching for something
that needs me here ♪
♪ Oh. California dreamin' ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Dream on. dream on ♪
♪ So keep holding me. baby ♪
♪ In LA ♪
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Our people waited all day and all night
freezing their asses off in the desert.
and your guy never made the drop.
I know and I apologize.
You sure he made the pickup?
Yeah. the Colombians confirmed
that he came and went yesterday.
So what?
The plane crashed?
No. I'm sorry that I wasted your time.
Just give me a few more days.
Sup. Peaches?
All quiet on the western front?
Come on. let's go to Franklin's room.
Boy. you need to relax with all that.
Shit. I can't relax.
I'm ready to go. Wanda.
Ladies. I would like y'all
to meet Franklin Saint.
AKA our Savior. AKA
the Big Black Apostle.
What's goin' on. baby? Come on.
Franklin's fine. aight?
Nice to meet you. ladies.
- What's up. Unc?
- Sup. nephew.
God damn!
I don't know how you got the energy.
If I got to spend my
days in that cookhouse.
I sure as hell ain't
spending my nights in here.
Hey. Peaches!
I don't need no chaperone. Jerome.
Looking like that you need a bodyguard.
Huh? Peaches!
Hey. hey. make sure she
get to the club aight.
- Bye.
- Gimme a kiss.
Give Claudia a kiss for me too.
I will if you want.
Tell her to come by. see my tree.
She ain't interested in your tree.
She like pie. though.
And I'll tell her you said hi too.
♪ It's the joint ♪
♪ We're gonna prove to the world ♪
♪ That we're for real ♪
♪ We're gonna prove to everybody ♪
♪ We know the real deal.
we got golden voices ♪
♪ And hearts of steel
'cause with five emcees ♪
♪ We got to be real.
we're here for ♪
♪ The party people on Sugar Hill ♪
♪ So what's the deal ♪
Open this goddamn door!
The fuck is wrong with you?
Oh. nigga. you wanna
fuck on my goddamn...
Come on. man!
- Mm-hmm.
- Bitch. get yo ass up!
- Hey... Hey. man!
- Be cool!
Nigga. get yo ass!
Just go!
Grab his ass!
- Jesus and Luis?
- They lost faith.
They going back to Mexico.
They would have never
done this to my dad.
Or Ramiro.
We'll have to train new drivers.
Who aren't gonna stay around
either unless this works.
Floundering!
And they can smell it.
Stomper's gonna be pissed
if we go around him.
I'm not bringing this to that asshole
just so he can cut us out.
Cessna Caravan. 1.200
nautical mile range.
3.600-pound payload.
- And the compression test?
- Two weeks ago. All green.
Okay.
So it's the same deal as last time.
Have the seats removed and weighed.
- Uh. where's the seller?
- Ohio.
I'll wire the money first thing.
but there's still the matter
of who's going to fly it.
Preferably someone who
won't run off this time.
- Aero Services Aviation.
- Can we go secure?
- Yeah.
- Will you excuse me a minute?
Going secure.
Okay. what's going on?
Wanted to let you know
that the president's
requested $21 million
to finance operations
in Nicaragua for the upcoming year.
Uh. yeah. I mean. that's only...
3 million less than last year.
I could probably make
up the difference if I...
He's not gonna get it. Teddy.
Repeat that. please.
Congress isn't going to
approve any of the funds.
So that's it?
There's no ancillary support?
I mean. are there other
options on the table?
Besides you? No.
So now the question that I have to ask
is can you handle this?
Yes. sir.
I am very glad to hear you say that.
But Teddy. this will change things.
It now becomes imperative
that nothing implicate
company involvement in any capacity.
Is that understood?
So no access to the weapons depot?
No access to anything official.
Even me.
This now becomes something
compartmented between the two of us.
And what if something happens to you?
I will have records in my safe
of everything so that you'll be covered.
Okay.
We're counting on you. Teddy.
We believe in you and what you're doing.
Continue to make us proud. okay?
Thank you. sir.
I will.
- Hey. Gladys?
- Yeah.
- Kansas City.
- I'm sorry?
Have the plane delivered to Kansas City.
Kansas side. any small airport
west of downtown will do.
What's in Kansas City?
Sometimes these things happen.
Just saying. a little
heads up would be nice.
But I like seeing you. Frankie.
Even... even Leon here is growing on me.
You know how stressful it
is to ride through Encino
with this much fucking coin in a car?
Okay.
Maybe Leon is not growing on me so much.
I got a few ounces
lying around somewhere
so you don't feel I've wasted your time.
Muir.
go to the stash. see what
you can find for Frankie.
You got it.
You know...
not too long ago you were happy
with just a few hundred dollars.
How we grow. huh.
Likes weeds.
Hey.
Friday.
Come over for Shabbat
dinner. wear a nice coat.
Come on. Franklin. You have money now.
Get yourself a nice coat.
- Avi! Avi!
- What?
- What'd he say?
- Hey. what's going on?
- LAPD! Hands up!
- Hands up!
- Don't run!
- Don't run.
- Faster! Move. Move.
- Hey! Against the wall.
Right there. don't move!
Hey. stop!
Everything is okay. Hello. Officer.
Stop! Stop right there!
Freeze!
Hey. don't fucking shoot. all right?
Hands behind your head.
- Think you can run. huh?
- Get the fuck off me.
- Hey!
- Fuck off!
I said hands behind your head.
You got a problem?
Punk kid. Think you can run from me?
Shut the fuck up.
Your boy's in business with
a Babe Ruth motherfucker.
That dude. Avi? Hitting
him with possession
with intent to go along
with a hefty gun charge.
In terms y'all laymans can understand.
that boy fucked.
What about Leon?
Hit him with a 69PC.
- The fuck is a 69PC...
- Felony evading.
Why the fuck you ain't say that then?
'Cause I'ma fucking
professional. J-rome.
No. you's a moron. Biscuit.
Look. Least they ain't trying
to rope him in on a
possession of weapons beef.
Now the bad news is.
your boy's got priors.
and because it's a felony. bail's 50.
Thousand.
Ain't 50 hundred. nigga.
- I want him out.
- Gonna need 10% down.
Cash. collateral. whatever.
Shit. 5.000 ain't shit.
- Yeah. it is.
- It is.
It's a lot. Tyrone.
I'm gonna need a minute
to get that for you.
Hey. ain't my boy in there.
Do what you gotta do.
Nephew. you got the five Gs on you now.
Let's get this shit done.
I don't want those two
knowing what I'm holding.
Tyrone's straight. he always has been.
You getting paranoid.
Avi and Leon are locked up.
And I just spent the whole of yesterday
running around Encino
with 42 Gs in a duffel bag
trying to find a cab or a
bus before the cops found me.
So yeah...
Maybe I'm a little on edge.
Well. with Avi in the clink.
you know where we gonna
get some more coke?
We wanna see Vuelvas and Chumacho.
Tell them Lucia Villanueva's here.
They know my family.
They used to buy marijuana
from my dad and my tio.
Hey.
_
If you're not interested. we'll leave.
Thank you for seeing us.
Cocaine.
but rocked-up.
smokable.
and cheap.
It's moving like
wildfire in South Central
and it's about to
take off in the barrio.
It's gonna be bigger than heroine.
more profitable.
Right now it's being sold by
mayates in Pico-Union.
I've been in business with
Stomper and the Monarcas.
But I'm bringing this to you.
There's money to be made.
I know it.
You say it's good.
Let's see.
_
Okay. wait.
You see the key to this game. Lucas.
is a steady hand and laser focus.
of which I have both.
Your problem is you're thinking
about Bethany's titties.
and how if I whip your
ass right now in public
you're not gonna get to see 'em.
And because you're thinking about that
and not concentrating on the shot.
you're gonna miss that shot.
Resulting in me whipping your ass
and coincidentally.
you not getting to
see Bethany's titties.
Think you mean ironically.
What was that?
Uh. you said. uh. "Coincidentally not
getting to see Bethany's titties."
But I think what you meant to say was.
"Ironically not getting
to see Bethany's titties."
The circumstance you're describing
being one of irony. and not coincidence.
Hey. Bethany.
Matt. wanna tell your friend
to stop talking about my tits?
Are you finished?
You gonna take a shot.
or keep doing a hatchet
job on the English language?
- Oh.
- Ha-ha.
- Wow.
- Hmm.
The weapons are flowing South.
Contras are pushing back.
That's how you're funding this?
Not all of it. but yeah.
- That...
- Yeah. that's fucked up.
Even for the CIA. that's fucked up.
Okay. okay.
Look. I... all that I need is a stopgap.
I just need someone reliable who can fly
the loads till I find
a permanent replacement.
That's it.
- How long?
- A month.
Two months. tops.
I'm sure Bethany will still be waiting
here for you when you get back.
He's not doing well. Teddy.
Jesus Christ.
Looked like he was doing fine to me.
- You're spying on us now?
- Here.
This should buy whatever help
he needs until you get back.
'Cause you're not gonna
see him when you're here.
I already saw him. Matt.
- I already saw him.
- Through the window.
Yeah. and they're spotless.
by the way. Great work.
Still got you washing 'em
with vinegar once a week?
It would mean a lot to him.
I don't give a fuck what
it would mean to him.
I really don't and
I'm sorry. But. listen.
it's you I came back
for. You understand?
I have a Cessna Caravan
waiting in a hangar at Fairfax Airport.
She's sexy as hell. She's ready to go.
All I need is someone to fly her.
You sure about this?
Because when I came back from 'Nam.
nobody had any idea what the point was.
For those people down there
and for us here it's important.
If we win this war we can
change the course of history.
And this war. we can win.
Hey. he still ain't out?
- Any minute. man.
- Tyrone in there now.
Where was I?
Uh. you was gettin' ready
to ruin the rest of the fucking movie.
Damn right. and he go.
"Say hello to my little friend."
Get him. motherfucker.
Yo. he's bad. I seen this shit twice.
Yeah. cuz.
- So he live?
- What?
Nah man. everybody in
that motherfucker die.
What's wrong with you. Jerome?
Man. you got crabs or something?
I don't like being out in front
of this motherfucking place. God damn.
- Amen.
- Ah.
This fool.
So when you drop the soap.
do you bend over to pick it up
or do you squat? Like how do you...
How does that work?
- This motherfucker.
- What's up. man?
Hey. y'all make sure this
little nigga don't run. you hear?
Who the fuck you talking to?
All right. playa.
Look. y'all need me again.
and it sound like you will.
you know where I'm at.
- They sweat you hard?
- Some.
You give 'em my social?
Name. number. address.
Appreciate that. man.
So what you want. huh?
Drink? Lap dance?
Wanda ain't come with y'all. huh?
Oh. no. man. she havin'
a little trouble walking.
Spent a little time with
her while you was gone.
Oh. you want to fuck with
me after I just got out. huh?
Nah. she wanted to fuck with us.
Oh. really? So I have to
beat all y'alls ass. huh?
Miguel.
He's out there somewhere.
All right.
Gustavo.
Still nothing?
Not in the States or in Mexico.
It's like he's vanished
off the face of the planet.
Maybe he has.
You know...
Pedro ran for a reason. Hmm?
He may never come back.
We killed his father.
He's not gonna let that go.
Boy. we was talking
about you last night.
All good. I hope.
Your homegirl Tanosse was up in here.
With your name in her mouth.
I did not know you two was acquainted.
Yeah. we used to kick
it back in the day.
So she said.
Let me get you a drink.
If Tanosse in here. I take
it Bobo back in the pen?
Yup.
She been hearing rumors
that you on the rise.
Yeah...
well. I got other shit
on my mind than pussy.
Making you a rarity amongst young men.
Come on. let me talk to you.
Hey!
- Hey. what the motherfuck?
- What the fuck?
Shit!
- There we go. Peaches.
- What the fuck happened?
How they get in?
Back door.
Somebody didn't lock that shit?
Somebody left that shit unlocked?
They jimmied the shit.
And Peaches. you ain't hear it?
And so what? You just kill
some motherfuckers in my house?
You ain't wanna scare 'em off first?
- What you gonna do that for?
- I ain't asking you!
- Well. I'm answering you!
- Stop!
Fucking stop. Keep your voices down.
Who the fuck are they?
Fuck.
It's motherfucking Biscuit.
That ain't Tyrone.
That's Jamal. That's
Biscuit older brother.
Biscuit's older brother.
who's paranoid now. Unc?
I told you not to mention
that fucking money!
They wouldn't even thought
twice about this shit
if you ain't make a big
deal of it. God damn.
I told you not to keep that
fucking money in our house!
Wanna talk about this now?
Hey. look. if nosy-ass
Shirley heard the shots.
then the cops is
probably on the way now.
God damn.
So now what you gonna do?
- Fuck.
- Huh?
Me and Jerome go and load up the bodies.
Drive 'em out.
Bury 'em.
You two. stay here. clean this shit up.
Sun rises.
this never happened.
I'm with that shit.
Come on.
This shit is fucking crazy.
Why ain't they back yet?
Gotta dig.
Shit takes time.
How you know?
This house ain't gonna
never be the same.
Mm.
You know. we should probably
get some bars on the windows.
And new doors.
- That them?
- Nah. they wouldn't knock.
You expecting somebody?
At 8:00 in the morning?
- Ah. shit.
- What?
One second.
Mel.
Something wrong?
Nah. I'm all right. I just...
Go on. 'Sup?
I just...
I was gonna come by
yesterday on the actual day.
But then I didn't know if I should.
In the end it just ain't feel right
not wishing you happy birthday.
You have fun?
Yeah. Yeah. we did.
We. uh. had a little party.
Nothing crazy.
I just came to give you this.
Happy birthday. Franklin.
Hope it was a good day.
Hey. uh...
you wanna go get some
breakfast or something?
Can't. school.
It's cool. Uh. I'll walk with you then.
I don't think that's a good idea.
- I just want to talk for...
- Franklin.
My dad's been hearing about you too
and don't want me nowhere near you.
Someone will see.
Hey. uh...
you or Andre.
talk to my moms at all?
She and my dad spend some time together.
I see her here and there.
How she doing?
Her heart's broken. Franklin.
How you think she doing?
Take care of yourself. okay?
_
Gracias.
This place is a shit hole.
You know who I am?
_
You bring all this in?
From our family's farms in Mexico.
Then we sell it wholesale.
You bring it through. uh.
border checkpoints or
you have your own routes?
I thought. uh. you were here
to talk about this new drug.
I'm here to talk about
whatever the fuck I want.
We have our own routes.
My father and uncle created them.
Mm-hmm.
They're dead now. right?
Is that right?
Mm-hmm.
If they weren't. what do you think
they'd say about this new product?
I think they'd see a
new business opportunity.
My boys agree with you.
They like this new rock cocaine.
Not me.
From what I seen. it makes people crazy.
_
Right? Keeps 'em calm. obedient.
which we control.
It also mean getting into
business with the mayates
and that could cause some problems.
This drug is gonna catch on
whether we're in it or not.
And if we're not...
that's a lot of money going
to those mayates
and not us.
leaving our people weaker.
Is that what you're worried about?
Our people?
Among other things.
Empowering Mexicans in this country.
Ensuring we have a voice
that cannot be ignored.
I believe this drug is the future.
And I believe it so deeply
I'm willing to front all the product.
Take on all the financial risk.
The decision is yours.
How was the flight?
Uh. it was as smooth
as a stripper's ass.
It was... fine.
You must be Matt.
And you are?
You can call me Mrs. Warren.
Could I call you something else?
No.
Can I speak with you
privately for a minute?
Anything you can say to him
you can say in front of me.
Yeah. it's all right. Gladys. Go ahead.
I still hadn't heard back from Avi
so I went by his house.
And... I think we have a problem.
It's a nice spot.
Any opportunity to
get out from that desk.
So this bust. this wasn't the result
of surveillance or a long-term op?
Started with a murdered
rich kid in Studio City.
Now we got the DEA. the FBI. and ATF
all fighting for who's gonna
take the lead on our bust.
You mind if I keep this copy?
Yeah. be my guest.
Thanks as always. Solo.
Coke's officially gone.
We got enough rock for maybe
another day or two. but that's it.
What about you. Rob?
You know how hard it is to find someone
to get you more than two kilos a week
who isn't full of shit?
He's trying to rip you off.
he's trying to kill you...
Yeah. yeah. whatever. man.
Anything from you two?
Nigga. you want a
chopped-up key for 25 grand?
Guy just a motherfucker.
Nigga. it was your connect.
I mean. it's like the
white boy. Rob. say.
There's lotta bullshit
out here. Frankie.
Okay.
First thing in the morning.
we head up to Oakland.
Visit Swim.
Get enough rock to tide us over.
Maybe even talk our
way into they connect.
Set up a pipeline south.
That's what we're gonna do.
I'm down.
Same.
Good.
Get some rest. man.
We'll link up at
Jerome's in the morning.
So what do you tell them?
The LAPD?
Oh. there's no them.
it's just this one guy.
This detective. he's the CIA
liaison at the department.
Hey. please don't open
that. Don't open that.
- So you're not worried at all?
- Worried about what?
About that guy. Avi.
deciding to roll on you.
Not really. I mean. even if he did.
they'd just be chasing Reed Thompson.
Who's that?
Exactly.
Oh.
So do I get an alias too?
Mm-hmm.
And you should start calling me Reed.
Okay. Reed.
If you're in the clear.
what's the problem?
The problem is. we're about import
50 keys of Colombian White.
I got no one to buy it.
So we need to find a drug dealer.
Talked to Claudia again. about the club.
- Mm.
- Offered her a blank check.
She ain't gonna sell. huh?
You know there's other
ways I could push her out.
Like how?
She got cops on the payroll
so it ain't like you
can just shut it down.
And you ain't gonna kill
her. so what else is there?
Hey...
- can I ask you something?
- Mm-hmm.
You know I noticed you've been spending
a lot of time over there.
With her.
- Is that a question?
- Look...
It ain't my business how you
and Jerome live your lives.
I'm just sayin' if you
falling for Claudia.
it's bad for business.
That's a problem.
You know that.
Or maybe I'm just getting close to her
trying to figure out a way
to get my hands on that club.
Seeing as how you seem to be unable.
Look. Look. Look.
I'ma handle it. okay?
I promise.
I mean. it might not be
a Christmas present. but...
I'ma get it done. okay?
I'm gonna piss.
Anything else you want to tell me?
Oso?
Who goes there?
It's me.
Pedro?
Hello. prima.
Environmental groups claims
that by the year 2000
a quarter of the world's
energy could cover
renewable sources. such
as the sun and wind.
Although much of the technology needed
to make such sources
viable is not yet...
- Hey. you okay?
- I'm good.
Can you hear me? I'm so sorry. man.
Are... How is your neck?
It's good. It's good.
Sorry about this. kid.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm